Giovanni

Pasini

Via Antonio Cantore 48 25128, Brescia(BS)

(+39)366 3032012 gpasini93@gmail.com

About me

Graduated in computer science with a focus on programming.

Work experience in the welding industry and managing computer networks.

I am always ready to help and listen to my clients and colleagues. I am reliable and open to new experiences.

Experience

Web Development Intern

2024 - PRESENTE, Taipei, Taiwan

- Two-Month Experience through Rotary New Generations Service Exchange
- I followed the development of the front-end part in the company, learning about daily activities and the project structure of the CRM system.
- I studied various programming languages (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, React, SQL) in person through courses recommended by the staff.
- I used intercultural communication skills to interact with various staff members who had different levels of English proficiency.
- I gained insights into Taiwanese work culture by participating in various team events and building connections with colleagues.

Freelance / Web Developer

2022 - PRESENT, Italy

- Website creation using the WordPress platform, utilizing knowledge of HTML and CSS.
- Researching and utilizing various plugins for website development, according to client requirements.

Proxi srl / IT Manager and Welding technician

2013 - 2023, Brescia

- Website management and maintenance of company computers.
- Creation of surveillance systems using cameras and specialized sensors.
- Analysis of malfunctions and repair of various types of welding machines.
- Collaboration with colleagues to find the best solution.
- Time management based on workload.
- Warehouse management responsibilities.

Education

Istituto tecnico superiore Piamarta / Computer Systems

2007 - 2013, Brescia

Studied programming languages: C++, Java, HTML, CSS, PHP, DOS. Learned electronics and how to diagnose and repair computers.

Udemy / The Web Developer Bootcamp 2024

2024 - 2024, Online

Javascript programming update.

React, Node, Express and MongoDB.

I have deepened my knowledge of website creation by incorporating React, Node, Express, and MongoDB into my programming skills.

Udemy / The Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery

2023, Online

Learned programming in Javascript. First approach to React, Redux, NodeJS. Get better in Web Development, Full Stack.

Udemy / The Complete Python Bootcamp

2022 - 2023, Online

Learned programming in Python.

First approach to data science, creating games and applications.

Deepened my knowledge of website development.

Languages

English B1/B2

Italian C2- Mother tongue